In a country where
there's no place for the poor,
and no consequences for the rich,
maybe, the verdict isn't from the court,
but instead,
it's up to the amount of money you've got.
I think we can't continue
if you don't speak the truth.
No matter how many times I speak,
I'll say the same thing.
I didn't cheat on the exam.
Only you, the headmaster, blame me.
It's just as you see. That's why
I had to invite you here, Mr. Songkiat.
But you don't have any proof.
Then why don't you
just force me to confess?
You didn't have to call my dad
for this mess.
Apologize to the headmaster now.
Dad!
Minnie.
I'm sorry.
Look at her and speak nicely.
I'm sorry, Madam Headmaster.
But about cheating on the exam,
that's a serious matter for our school.
Yes, I'd like to donate
1,000,000 baht to the school,
for my daughter's bad behavior this time.
However, Minnie will be punished.
I understand that.
Would you like me
to write a check in your name?
You…
will have to clean the restroom
in Building 4 for the whole semester.
Understood, Minnie?
Yes, ma'am.
Why did you hit me?
If I didn't, you would've been expelled.
That's fine. I don't care.
But I do. I'm sick and tired
of finding you schools to study.
-Someone must have told the teacher.
-Hey!
Will you stop babbling?
You want to embarrass me more?
Well… but…
the headmaster has no proof,
so how could she punish me?
You're stupid. You copied every answer.
How could she not know?
And why can't other people think
that I might be the one who got copied?
I'm not the headmaster.
You don't have to lie to me.
I know well enough that you…
you never admit your wrongdoings.
Be more clever.
I'll take your car,
and you'll be grounded for a month.
You can't leave the house
after 6 p.m., period.
Are you out of your mind?
You can't do this.
I just lost 1,000,000 baht,
so you wouldn't be expelled.
-But--
-But what?
Hey there, Minnie!
Je, I'm coming to pick you up.
To where? Are you driving now?
Yes.
Oh, and what about
your dad's 6 p.m. curfew?
Let him do it himself.
There's no fucking proof.
How could I be punished?
Oh, right!
Or… was it actually Ploen?
She let me copy her exam
and then told the teacher.
Why would she do that?
Or she doesn't like
the fact that you're richer?
When you paid,
did you use internet banking?
That could be evidence.
No. I paid in cash.
But that's true. If there's no proof,
how could the headmaster punish you?
That's not right.
No.
That's why we need to break
Mr. Songkiat's curfew
and celebrate till dawn, okay?
All right. I'll come along.
That's my girl!
I'm about to pass by the school.
Be there in a sec. See you soon, girl.
Okay. See you.
Bye-bye, Miss Minnie.
Nanno.
Ploen.
Minnie. Help me.
Or… was it actually Ploen?
She let me copy her exam
and then told the teacher.
Why don't you help your friend, Minnie?
Ploen.
Dad. Help me.
This just came in.
There has been an accident,
a car crashed into a school pick-up.
There are students…
These are the names
of the four students killed.
They are all 17 to 18 years old,
and it is speculated
they're the schoolmates of the suspect.
We'll have an interview with her dad.
Hey, mister… are you Minnie's dad?
A little interview, please.
So what do you have to say
about the accident?
Excuse me. My daughter is still in shock.
Right now,
we're not ready for an interview.
She's shocked because she was intoxicated?
There's no alcohol involved.
-No.
-You said there's no alcohol.
Have the police tested that?
I told you there's none.
And we're not ready for an interview.
It's still the news
that we're following right now.
I believe that a lot of people
want to hear more about this.
How will it turn out? We'll…
See? See what you've done?
I told you not to leave the house.
Why did you leave?
I didn't mean
for all this to happen, really.
But…
suddenly, the brakes didn't work.
Here we go again.
Are you denying it again?
I'm not lying, Dad.
The brakes weren't really working.
She said that the brakes weren't working.
Why don't you just believe her?
The brakes weren't working?
You know,
if I hadn't taken out the wine bottle,
she would've ended up in jail right now.
Really, dear?
But the brakes really weren't working.
Dad, do you really think
I wanted to hit someone?
That's right, honey.
Let's find a way to help her.
You… How many times
do you want me to clean up your mess?
Dad, you have to help me.
If you're charged with a crime,
the company's stocks will completely drop.
This time, you just shut your mouth…
and do everything as I say.
Understood?
Here she comes.
How dare she still come to school?
I bet she was drunk last night.
How can she act like nothing happened?
Je…
Minnie.
It happened because of
a brake malfunction.
Minnie wasn't drunk-driving.
And the reason I'm saying this is because…
Minnie has never touched
any alcoholic drinks.
-Bullshit.
Is he for real? That's a shameless lie.
She's never touched alcohol?
I've seen her drink before.
She was so drunk, she threw up
at the new year's party, remember?
Everybody in school saw that.
But I think she'll get away with it,
you believe me?
Well, her dad is that rich…
Give Minnie an opportunity
to prove herself this time.
MINNIE. TO HELL WITH MINNIE,
THAT QUADRUPLE MURDERER.
SHE KILLED FOUR PEOPLE AND STILL GOT AWAY.
EACH OF US STABS HER, AND SHE'S A GONER.
SHE SHOULD DIE FOUR TIMES.
Ploen was a good girl.
PARENTS OF PLOEN, ONE OF THE FOUR VICTIMS.
When she got home,
she helped me with chores.
Helped me with selling stuff.
We put our hopes on her.
I'd like the court to be just,
and not side with what's wrong.
And has Minnie, the suspect,
come to apologize to you two?
Never.
And this is what
one of the deceased's families feels.
We'll have to see how this case ends.
Will it be similar to previous accidents
caused by other famous families?
That is unknown. Now…
This is the testimony
drafted by the lawyer. Memorize it.
"The pick-up driver parked unsafely"?
Do as I say. Don't ask.
You know I'm not a good liar.
Not a good liar?
You cheated on a test,
yet you denied everything.
But it's not the same. I can't do it.
All these times,
the whole family has been frowned upon,
I'm embarrassed enough already.
Do you want me to have more of this?
And you want more?
THE DEFENDANT CLAIMS THAT SHE WAS
DRIVING WITHIN THE LEGAL SPEED LIMIT.
THE DEFENDANT WAS CAREFUL
AS A PERSON OF ORDINARY PRUDENCE.
GIVEN THAT THE AREA WAS DARK,
THE VICTIMS WERE ALSO RESPONSIBLE…
CONSIDERING THE SCENE, IT WAS CAUSED
BY THE RECKLESS ACTIONS OF THE VICTIMS.
How did you feel after the first hearing?
Excuse me, ma'am.
She can't give an interview right now,
as it can jeopardize the case.
Was it from this bottle
that you drank that night?
So, did you have
any alcoholic drinks that night?
-So, did you drink?
-Did you?
Please answer the question.
Can you answer the question?
Please give us an answer.
WHO WANTS TO SEE #MINNIE4BODIES
PAY FOR HER CRIME, RAISE YOUR HAND!
LET'S VOTE FOR LESSONS
TO TEACH #MINNIE4BODIES.
CUT HER FACE. #MINNIE4BODIES
I'LL KNOCK HER TEETH OUT.
#MINNIE4BODIES
IF I HAD A BRAT LIKE #MINNIE4BODIES,
I'D CHOKE HER TO DEATH.
KILL AND BUTCHER HER #MINNIE4BODIES
Je. Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not.
Don't say you're not.
Even if the others hate me, fuck it.
But that night, you talked to me.
But…
But what? Just say it.
I told you the brakes
weren't really working.
You don't believe me?
Je. You must believe me.
Yes. I believe you. But…
-I…
-But… what?
What is it? Tell me.
-I just…
-Yes?
…see those four people
behind you all the time.
Nanno.
Where are they?
Aren’t you just so impatient
like your daughter?
Are you sure there aren’t any more copies?
I don't know where you got these photos
because I gave orders to the police
to delete them.
I'll give you money, just this one time.
If these pics appear again,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Back to the news
which is the talk of the town,
the "4-Death Minnie" case.
There has been criticism
as to the transparency of this case.
If you get away with it,
I’ll kill you with my own hands.
-Why don't you help your friend, Minnie?
-Help.
I see those four girls
following me all the time.
I can't take it anymore, Mom.
Calm down, dear.
You might be overthinking it.
If you said the brakes weren't working,
then the brakes weren't working.
It's not your fault.
Others scold you so much
that you think it's your fault.
The thing you need to worry about now
is us getting sued.
Do as your dad says. Understood?
Now, to the case
which has the public's attention.
Today, at the youth court,
the court will render a judgment
on the "4-Death Minnie" case.
The incident was caused by
the recklessness of both parties.
The pick-up was parked at a dangerous spot
which was prone to accidents.
The court has ordered Minnie to pay
damages to the deceased's families
amounting to 300,000 baht each,
and engage in
a 300-hour community service.
Don't be afraid, Minnie. Don't be.
You're guilty.
Die. You killed other people.
-You made them die.
-I'm not guilty.
-You're guilty.
-What's the matter, Minnie?
What's wrong?
Hey, sir. The brakes won't work!
Welcome to
Who Wants Minnie to Pay for Her Crime,
Raise Your Hand Show!
Minnie, do you know that
many people want to see you?
You're more famous than a celebrity!
Come on out!
Who are you?
Just ordinary people
who want to see you get punished.
Minnie, do you know
how many people like this are out there?
Come on! Are you ready
to hear the audience's judgment?
For the 4th prize,
"I want to see Minnie's legs broken,
because the legs
that didn't hit the brakes
are the cause of this whole tragedy."
Go on!
Let's continue. For the 3rd prize,
"I want to slap her
until all her teeth fall off and die
for her shameless bullshitting!"
Bullshitting? Well, that's true!
You've been slapped for quite some time,
but your teeth haven't fallen off yet.
Should you guys change the way to do it?
Your teeth are out…
but you're not dead yet.
If you're not dead,
then we can't go on to the next prize.
Why are you so surprised, Minnie?
The 2nd prize is just coming.
The owner of this prize is
Ploen's dad and mom.
Welcome!
You're guilty,
but you're not admitting it, are you?
I'm not guilty.
The brakes weren't really working.
I'm not guilty!
Dad, there are people out there
wanting to kill us. We have to run.
Don't be afraid, Minnie.
It's all taken care of.
No one is going to kill us.
Really, Dad?
Of course. Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
No one can hurt you.
Dad.
Dad, I can't breathe. Dad!
Dad, let go. Dad!
Didn't you realize it by now?
No one can hurt you,
except for your own dad.
Let's go on. The first prize is…
"I want to choke you to death, you brat,
for causing me trouble every day."
That's from Mr. Songkiat,
and he is Minnie's dad!
Dad, let go. Dad!
Dad.
Don't be afraid, Minnie.
This will hurt just a bit.
Dad.
How are you doing, Minnie?
If you had admitted what you did,
you wouldn't be in this condition.
But Minnie,
you've been dead just three times.
Aren't you tired yet?
Get some rest.
Wow, there's a TV.
That's nice.
And now, we have important evidence
that could potentially make the police
reopen the "4-Death Minnie" case.
It's this photo
that was sent to our reporter.
And we're seeing it now.
IMPORTANT EVIDENCE FOUND,
"4-DEATH MINNIE" CASE REOPENED
In addition to the photo you see,
there's also an audio clip,
which seems to be
the voice of Mr. Songkiat,
Minnie's father.
He's acting like
he's threatening the anonymous person
to not publish this photo.
I'll give you money, just this one time.
If these pics appear again,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Right now, Mr. Songkiat…
won't be able to help you anymore.
The only way all this will end…
is…
The weather's so nice tonight.
Here we meet again, Nanno.
Hello, Yuri.
Subtitle translation by:
Tanada Hantaweewatana